towerfcu.org 2019-06-05

# FACTS

                                                                                                   Rev. 08/2017
                       WHAT DOES TOWER FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
  FACTS                DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
  Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                       gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires
                       us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please
                       read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
  What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or
                       service you have with us. This information can include:
                       ■ Social Security number and name
                       ■ Account balances and payment history
                       ■ Credit history and credit scores
  How?                 All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their
                       everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can
                       share their members’ personal information; the reasons Tower Federal Credit Union
                       chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                           Does Tower Federal
Reasons we can share your personal information                                     Can you limit this sharing?
                                                           Credit Union share?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                  Yes                         No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you                           Yes                         Yes
For joint marketing with other financial companies                  Yes                         Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your transactions and experiences                 Yes                         Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your creditworthiness                             No                    We do not share
For our affiliates to market to you                                 Yes                         Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                  No                           No
  To limit             ■ Call 301-497-7000 or 800-787-8328
  our sharing          ■ Visit us online: towerfcu.org and go to Contact Us
                       Please note:
                       If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date
                       we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your
                       information as described in this notice.
                       However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
  Questions?           Call 301-497-7000 or 800-787-8328 or go to towerfcu.org.

Who we are
Who is providing this notice?              Tower Federal Credit Union
What we do
How does Tower Federal Credit Union        To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information?           and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                           These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                           and buildings.
How does Tower Federal Credit Union        We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?
                                           ■ open an account or deposit money
                                           ■ pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                           ■ use your credit or debit card
                                           We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                           credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?             Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                           ■ sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                              about your creditworthiness
                                           ■ affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                           ■ sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                           State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                           rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing          Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
for an account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                 Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                           financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                           ■ Our affiliate includes Tower Wealth Management®.
Nonaffiliates                              Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can
                                           be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Joint marketing                            A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies
                                           that together market financial products or services to you.
                                           ■ Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance and
                                              other financial services companies, i.e. CUNA Mutual® Group.
Other important information
You may opt out of receiving marketing information from Tower Federal Credit Union or through its joint
marketing agreements. Follow the instructions in the “To limit our sharing” section of this notice.
                                                                                                       2133 8/17
